{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Entrepreneur",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Week-3",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Week-3"
    ]
  },
"quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the means by which the exchange of goods and services takes place as a result of buyers and sellers being in contact with one another?",
      "answer": "Market",
      "choices": [
        "Value Proposition",
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Target Market",
        "Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market and Propositions",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a business or marketing statement that summarizes why a consumer should buy a company's product or use its service?",
      "answer": "Value Proposition",
      "choices": [
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Market Targeting",
        "Customer Requirements",
        "Value Proposition"
      ],
      "reference": "Market and Propositions",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to how you sell your product or services to your customer?",
      "answer": "Unique Selling Proposition",
      "choices": [
        "Value Proposition",
        "Market Targeting",
        "Customer Requirements",
        "Unique Selling Proposition"
      ],
      "reference": "Market and Propositions",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a stage in market identification process that aims to determine the buyers with common needs and characteristics?",
      "answer": "Market Targeting",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Market Targeting"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the market segment that an entrepreneurial venture intends to serve?",
      "answer": "Prospect customers",
      "choices": [
        "Target Market",
        "Buyers",
        "Suppliers",
        "Prospect customers"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market divides the total market according to geographical location?",
      "answer": "Geographic segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation",
        "Geographic segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market is divided based on consumers?",
      "answer": "Demographic Segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market is divided in terms of what customers think and believe?",
      "answer": "Psychological Segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market is divided according to customers' behavior patterns as they interact with a company?",
      "answer": "Behavioral Segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the specific characteristics that customers need from a product or a service?",
      "answer": "Customer requirements",
      "choices": [
        "Service Requirement",
        "Output Requirement",
        "Value Proposition",
        "Customer requirements"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of customer requirement consists of elements like on-time delivery, service with a smile, and easy-payment?",
      "answer": "Service Requirement",
      "choices": [
        "Output Requirement",
        "Customer requirements",
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Service Requirement"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of customer requirement encompasses all aspects of how a customer expects to be treated while purchasing a product?",
      "answer": "Service Requirement",
      "choices": [
        "Output Requirement",
        "Customer requirements",
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Service Requirement"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of customer requirement can take the form of product specifications like the loudness and clarity of a pair of speakers?",
      "answer": "Output Requirement",
      "choices": [
        "Service Requirement",
        "Customer requirements",
        "Value Proposition",
        "Output Requirement"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the approximate number of sellers and buyers in a particular market?",
      "answer": "Market Size",
      "choices": [
        "Total Available Market",
        "Served Available Market",
        "Target Market",
        "Market Size"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the market size answers the question \"how big is the universe\"?",
      "answer": "Total Available Market",
      "choices": [
        "Served Available Market",
        "Target Market",
        "Market Size",
        "Total Available Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the market size answers the question \"how many can I reach with my sales channel\"?",
      "answer": "Served Available Market",
      "choices": [
        "Total Available Market",
        "Target Market",
        "Market Size",
        "Served Available Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the market size for a startup answers the question \"who will be the most likely buyers\"?",
      "answer": "Target Market",
      "choices": [
        "Total Available Market",
        "Served Available Market",
        "Market Size",
        "Target Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    }
  ]
}